Mark Winston fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Undergraduate Semester in Dialogue and Centre for Dialogue records, 2000 - 2014; F-174-9; 65.8 cm of textual records 3 photographs 2 optical discs
  - Centre for Dialogue, 2002 - 2012; F-174-9-2; 25.2 cm of textual records 1 optical disc
    - Dialogue: grad programs, 2002 - 2003; F-174-9-2-0-13 (Archival box - small 174-94)
    - Jack Blaney Award for Dialogue - Centre for Dialogue Steering Committee, 2004 - 2012; F-174-9-2-0-14 (Archival box - small 174-94)